export const floatFishing = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1. The float is used to detect the presence of a bite.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '2. Float fishing is usually conducted in deep water bodies.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '3. Floats are only made of plastic.oldfish',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '4. Float fishing is most effective for catching carp.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5. The float should always be completely submerged.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '6. Float fishing is often used for catching small fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '7. Float fishing requires the use of a reel.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Float fishing is best conducted in still water.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: '9. Float fishing requires heavy tackle.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      '10. When float fishing, it is important to choose the correct weighting.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
];
